export const cards = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: 'apple',
    back: 'Яблоко',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: 'red',
    back: 'красный',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: 'green',
    back: 'зелёный',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: 'blue',
    back: 'синий',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: 'yellow',
    back: 'жёлтый',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: 'orange',
    back: 'оранжевый',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    front: 'purple',
    back: 'пурпурный',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    front: 'white',
    back: 'белый',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    front: 'black',
    back: 'чёрный',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    front: 'brown',
    back: 'коричневый',
  },
];
